Tufts Daily UP029
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Daily, 1989; UP029.010; 2 Volumes; 126 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 13; UP029.010.014.00018 (Volume 14)
    Aidekman Arts Center [1988-89]. Lawsuit with Somerville resumes.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 14; UP029.010.014.00019 (Volume 14)
    [Allocations Board] TEMS funding denied; Administration and TCUS negligentl; Letters (Senate Funding).
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 15; UP029.010.014.00020 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 16; UP029.010.014.00021 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 17; UP029.010.014.00022 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 21; UP029.010.014.00023 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 22; UP029.010.014.00024 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 23; UP029.010.014.00025 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 24; UP029.010.014.00026 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 27; UP029.010.014.00027 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 28; UP029.010.014.00028 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 01; UP029.010.014.00029 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 02; UP029.010.014.00030 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 03; UP029.010.014.00031 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 06; UP029.010.014.00032 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 07; UP029.010.014.00033 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 08; UP029.010.014.00034 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 09; UP029.010.014.00035 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 10; UP029.010.014.00036 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 13; UP029.010.014.00037 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 14; UP029.010.014.00038 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 15; UP029.010.014.00039 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 16; UP029.010.014.00040 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 27; UP029.010.014.00041 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 28; UP029.010.014.00042 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 29; UP029.010.014.00043 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 30; UP029.010.014.00044 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 March 31; UP029.010.014.00045 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 01; UP029.010.014.00046 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 03; UP029.010.014.00047 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 04; UP029.010.014.00048 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 05; UP029.010.014.00049 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 06; UP029.010.014.00050 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 07; UP029.010.014.00051 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 10; UP029.010.014.00052 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 11; UP029.010.014.00053 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 12; UP029.010.014.00054 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 13; UP029.010.014.00055 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 14; UP029.010.014.00056 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 18; UP029.010.014.00057 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 19; UP029.010.014.00058 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 20; UP029.010.014.00059 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 21; UP029.010.014.00060 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 24; UP029.010.014.00061 (Volume 14)
    Abortion 1988-1989. Pro-life (letter).; [Administration] Budget, etc. debated. pp. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 25; UP029.010.014.00062 (Volume 14)
    David Abravaya. Crafts Center coordinator's increase denied. [Allocations Board] ALBO members selected.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 26; UP029.010.014.00063 (Volume 14)
    [Administration] Service awards, p. 1, 3; Elizabeth [Liz] Amador service award recipient
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 27; UP029.010.014.00064 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 April 28; UP029.010.014.00065 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 May 01; UP029.010.014.00066 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, Commencement, 1989; UP029.010.014.00067 (Volume 14)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 August 31; UP029.010.015.00001 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Greeks establish alcohol orientation. [Alcohol Abuse] Lecture series; Mayer's Adress; GAMMA.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 05; UP029.010.015.00002 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 07; UP029.010.015.00003 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Shuffle follows resignations, p. 3; [American association of University professors] Justice department probes faculty salaries
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 11; UP029.010.015.00004 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Academic Resource Center; "Active Reading" course offered p.5.; [Activities and Organizations] ZBT's [Zeta Beta Tau's] no-pledging policy pp. 1, 14. "Active Reading," 1989-90. Academic Resource Center course; [Administration] Shuffle follows resignations, p. 1, 6 (Maxwell replacement).
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 12; UP029.010.015.00005 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 13; UP029.010.015.00006 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] service department search, p. 1; Free speech policy, p. 1, 11. [Alcohol Forum] Praised by Mayer.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 14; UP029.010.015.00007 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alessi, Kelley] Referendum: presidential election, TCU; new bylaw.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 15; UP029.010.015.00008 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Free speech policy, p. 1, 6: p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 18; UP029.010.015.00009 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 19; UP029.010.015.00010 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. MassPIRG: Toxics Use Reduction Act. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. MassPIRG; [Administration] Parking fee, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 20; UP029.010.015.00011 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    AIESEC [L'Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Commerciales] Tina Adolphsson in Warsaw, p 3; [Administration] Habitat builds homes, p. 1, 5.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 21; UP029.010.015.00012 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    AIESEC [L'Association Internationale des Etudiants en Sciences Economiques et Commerciales] Tina Adolphsson in Warsaw, p 7; Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Organizations and Administration expand recycling Revere Beach cleanup. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Judiciary officer shortage. Letters. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Judiciary officer shortage. Elections. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Senate. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Senate. Editorial. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Senate. Letters; [Administration] Parking tickets: letters re: free speech, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 22; UP029.010.015.00013 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Sexual harassment-Wessell, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 25; UP029.010.015.00014 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. SOAR [Students Organized Against Racism] continues. pp. 1, 5.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 26; UP029.010.015.00015 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Hosted Greek Olympics; [Administration] Free speech policy, p. 1, 8. [Alessi, Kelley] Referendum: presidential Election, TCU.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 27; UP029.010.015.00016 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 28; UP029.010.015.00017 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Academic Achievers [1989-90][Alpha Tau Omega]. Inter-Greek Council honors. Academic Honors; Academic achievers; P.5.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 September 29; UP029.010.015.00018 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 02; UP029.010.015.00019 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Afro-American Society] Protest Zaire leader at Harvard, p. 1, 12. [Alcohol Abuse] Lecture series.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 03; UP029.010.015.00020 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Ad Hoc committee on institutional policy] Racism policies. p. 1, 5. [Alessi, Kelley] (90) Free Speech Policy.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 04; UP029.010.015.00021 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Free speech policy suspended, p. 1, 15.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 05; UP029.010.015.00022 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [AIDS] Grant recipient, Norman Daniels. pp. 1, 5; "Am I my parents keeper?" Health issues book
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 06; UP029.010.015.00023 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Admissions 1989-90] Positions filled.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 10; UP029.010.015.00024 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    AFL-CIO 1988-89, Homeless march, pp 1, 11
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 11; UP029.010.015.00025 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] TLGBC coordinator approval, p. 1, 3.; [Advising] Reforms needed. pp. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 12; UP029.010.015.00026 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [American association of University professors] Increased involvement; [Admissions 1989-90] SAT's. [Administration] TLGBC coordinator approval (editorial), p. 2; "Freedom of speech vs..." keep campus harassment-free, p. 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 13; UP029.010.015.00027 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] "Health Study" of Greek system, p. 1, 11; [Marjorie Alt] Environmental conference
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 16; UP029.010.015.00028 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Aidekman Arts Center [1989-90]. Zoning disputes. [Alpha Sigma Phi] Healey playground completed.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 17; UP029.010.015.00029 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Afro-American Society] TCU-S allocations, p. 1, 2. Free Speech Policy Committee disbanded. [Allocations Board] MERIDIAN granted funding, p. 1.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 18; UP029.010.015.00030 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alpha Phi] Intergreek council block party, bake sale
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 19; UP029.010.015.00031 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 20; UP029.010.015.00032 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    David Abrevaya. Crafts Center denied funds; [Meeta Amand] China experience
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 23; UP029.010.015.00033 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 24; UP029.010.015.00034 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [American Institute of Chemical engineers] Denied funding; Phil Abruzzi. Power outage. [Allocations Board] TCU-S elects council chairs, p. 1, 12; [Amateur radio club] TCU-J bylaw
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 25; UP029.010.015.00035 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Defends Tufts lobbyists, p. 1, 2, 4, 8, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 26; UP029.010.015.00036 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 27; UP029.010.015.00037 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Language center construction, p. 13.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 30; UP029.010.015.00038 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 October 31; UP029.010.015.00039 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 01; UP029.010.015.00040 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Anner, Mark, wounded in labor union bombing in El Salvador, p. 13 [Alumni 1989-90].
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 02; UP029.010.015.00041 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Admissions] Policy does not need evaluation (letter). pp. 2, 5. [Admissions 1989-90] Policy does not need evaluation (letter). Anner, Mark wounded in labor union bombing in El Salvador, recovering p.16 [Alumni 1989-90].
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 03; UP029.010.015.00042 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 06; UP029.010.015.00043 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 07; UP029.010.015.00044 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [The Amateur radio society] Back and functioning after a six-year abscence [includes photo]
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 08; UP029.010.015.00045 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 09; UP029.010.015.00046 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Alpha Sigma Phi on probation.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 13; UP029.010.015.00047 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 14; UP029.010.015.00048 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 15; UP029.010.015.00049 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [American association of University professors] Faculty morale low; [American civil rights movement] Eyes on the prize II
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 16; UP029.010.015.00050 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 17; UP029.010.015.00051 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Admissions, Office of] Student Outreach Program. p. 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 20; UP029.010.015.00052 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 21; UP029.010.015.00053 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Admissions, Office of] SCOPE [Students of Color Outreach Progam] pp. 5, 11. Fraternities looking into unused special-interest house.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 27; UP029.010.015.00054 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 28; UP029.010.015.00055 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [African-American students] Myth of the "different Negro'", p. 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 29; UP029.010.015.00056 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Administration] Commuters displeased with parking policies, p. 1, 10; [Alumni association] Interimship program
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 November 30; UP029.010.015.00057 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [African-American Center] Panel discussion: "Health Care for the Community of Color", p. 5; [African-American Students] Letter of response, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 01; UP029.010.015.00058 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Phil Abruzzi. Carmichael Hall roaches to be exterminated; [African-American Students] Students continue to raise funds for the Ronald Blackburn Scholarship, p. 1; Letter of Thanks, p. 2.; [AIDS] A Day Without Art pp. 7, 8. Artists honor World AIDS Day, p. 7.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 04; UP029.010.015.00059 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    Beelzebub's live album being recorded by Bill Allen (A83). [Allocations Board] Revises spring budgeting schedule.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 05; UP029.010.015.00060 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    TCU backs coffee boycott. [Allocations Board] Budgeting: votes on funding.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 06; UP029.010.015.00061 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    TCU-J re-recognition policy, p. 1, 12. [Allocations Board] Club sports face cuts, p. 1, 9.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 07; UP029.010.015.00062 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Founders day
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 08; UP029.010.015.00063 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
    [Alpha Epsilon Pi] David Zaret elected IFC president. Administration] professors seek to diversify curriculum, p. 1, 11; [African-American Students] New courses on issues of race, sex, and gender, p. 1, 11.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 December 11; UP029.010.015.00064 (Volume UP029 Shared 1)
- Tufts Daily, 1989 -- 1990; UP029.011; 1.2 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 124 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 18; UP029.011.016.00001 (Volume 16)
    [Administration] Director of planning and facilities position eliminated, p. 1.; [AIDS] Protest in Goddard Chapel. pp. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 23; UP029.011.016.00002 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 25; UP029.011.016.00003 (Volume 16)
    [Admissions 1990] January Freshmen program eliminated. Activities and Organizations, 1989-90. Tufts Community Union Judiciary member Joseph Swimmer resigns; [Administration] Mayer pursues expansion, p. 1, 16; State may cut grants, p. 1, 16; Athletics budget may survive, p. 1; Tufts, Medford await court rule, p. 5; January freshmen program replaced with transfers, p. 5; Athletics may be spared, p. 1; [After Hours] Employee suspended, p. 1, 8.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 29; UP029.011.016.00004 (Volume 16)
    [Allocations Board] TCUJ recommends group's fund to be frozen, p. 1, 4.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 30; UP029.011.016.00005 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 January 31; UP029.011.016.00006 (Volume 16)
    [Allocations Board] Budgeting.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 01; UP029.011.016.00007 (Volume 16)
    Aidekman Arts Center [1989-90]. Zoning disputes.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 02; UP029.011.016.00008 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 05; UP029.011.016.00009 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 06; UP029.011.016.00010 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 07; UP029.011.016.00011 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 08; UP029.011.016.00012 (Volume 16)
    Activities and Organizations, 1988-89; 1989-90. "The Greek Gazette," Centerfold in Tufts Daily, February 8, 1990; [Administration] Financial aid cuts, diversity, p. 2, 3, 12; Goddard demonstration (letter), p. 2, 12; [After Hours] Cigarette sales banned, p. 1.
  - Tufts Daily, 1989 February 09; UP029.011.016.00013 (Volume 16)
    [Administration] Goddard demonstration, p. 2, 9. Aidekman Arts Center [1989-90]. Zoning disputes.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 12; UP029.011.016.00014 (Volume 16)
    [Administration] Pamela Allara leaves: positions eliminated, p. 1, 12; [After Hours] ban on cigarettes, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 13; UP029.011.016.00015 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 14; UP029.011.016.00016 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 15; UP029.011.016.00017 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 16; UP029.011.016.00018 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 20; UP029.011.016.00019 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 21; UP029.011.016.00020 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 22; UP029.011.016.00021 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 23; UP029.011.016.00022 (Volume 16)
    Action Through Awareness, 1990. Student sleepout for homeless.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 26; UP029.011.016.00023 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 27; UP029.011.016.00024 (Volume 16)
    [Albano, Salvatore R.] Financial aid; [American association of University professors] Editorial re: Robert Rotberg
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 February 28; UP029.011.016.00025 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] National policies banning kegs affects 6 fraternities; Frats ban kegs.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 01; UP029.011.016.00026 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Ad Hoc Committee for keg decision.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 02; UP029.011.016.00027 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 05; UP029.011.016.00028 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Theta Delta Chi loses recognition.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 06; UP029.011.016.00029 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Theta Delta Chi International suspends local chapter. [Allocations Board] Chair recommends no funds to Portfolio, p. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 07; UP029.011.016.00030 (Volume 16)
    Students skeptical about museum program's future.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 08; UP029.011.016.00031 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Theta Delta Chi plans appeal. [Allocations Board] Editorial re: Portfolio funding; letter, p. 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 09; UP029.011.016.00032 (Volume 16)
    Students skeptical about museum program's future (editorial). [Allocations Board] ALBO recommends Portfolio funding, p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 12; UP029.011.016.00033 (Volume 16)
    [Allocations Board] ALBO recommends Portfolio funding, recommends $40,000, p. 1, 6.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 13; UP029.011.016.00034 (Volume 16)
    [Alumnae Hall] Asbestos removed
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 14; UP029.011.016.00035 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 15; UP029.011.016.00036 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 16; UP029.011.016.00037 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 26; UP029.011.016.00038 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 27; UP029.011.016.00039 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 28; UP029.011.016.00040 (Volume 16)
    [Alcohol Abuse] Alcohol poisonings down.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 29; UP029.011.016.00041 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 March 30; UP029.011.016.00042 (Volume 16)
    Wyn Stevens Adair (TUSM faculty) dies in ski accident. pp. 1, 8
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 02; UP029.011.016.00043 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 03; UP029.011.016.00044 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 04; UP029.011.016.00045 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 05; UP029.011.016.00046 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 06; UP029.011.016.00047 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 09; UP029.011.016.00048 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 10; UP029.011.016.00049 (Volume 16)
    [Admissions 1990] Figures released. p. 1,4
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 11; UP029.011.016.00050 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 12; UP029.011.016.00051 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 13; UP029.011.016.00052 (Volume 16)
    [Admissions 1990] Tufts first to offer Community Sevice Option.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 17; UP029.011.016.00053 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 18; UP029.011.016.00054 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 19; UP029.011.016.00055 (Volume 16)
    [Administration] Admissions braces itself for '94 dip., p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 20; UP029.011.016.00056 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 23; UP029.011.016.00057 (Volume 16)
    [African-American Center] President of African American Society killed, p. 1, 14.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 24; UP029.011.016.00058 (Volume 16)
    [Allocations Board] ALBO chairs elected, p. 1, 13.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 25; UP029.011.016.00059 (Volume 16)
    [Allara, Pamela] Leaves for Brandeis.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 26; UP029.011.016.00060 (Volume 16)
    [African-American Center] Memorial for Anita Grifey, p. 1, 10.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 27; UP029.011.016.00061 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 April 30; UP029.011.016.00062 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, Commencement, 1990; UP029.011.016.00063 (Volume 16)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 August 30; UP029.011.017.00001 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Activities and Organizations] Torn Ticket II and 3P's [Pen, Paint, and Pretzels] pp. 7, 14; Greek system pp. 1, 8; TLGBC [Tufts Lesbian Gay and Bisexual Collective] p. 3; [Administration] GAMMA, p. 1, 8; Diversity film, p. 3.; [Admissions, Office of] Housing. pp. 1, 5, 6. [Alcohol Awareness] Jean Mayer- address.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 04; UP029.011.017.00002 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Administration] Austin, Jack-Associate Provost- died 6/25/90, p. 1, 5 (photo); Police contract unsettled, p. 1, 13; Trustees recommend limiting tuition, p. 1, 17; Mayer re:intolerance, p. 1, 15; Bobbie Knable, p. 1, 7; [African-American Center] Jewel Hairston Bell, director, died 8/04/90 (photo).
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 06; UP029.011.017.00003 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [African-American Center] Lack of Black Professors, p. 3, 17; [Alpha Omicron Pi] Acquires 123 house.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 10; UP029.011.017.00004 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    Access; Students gain "Access"; P.5; [Administration] State cuts reduce aid, p. 1, 16.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 12; UP029.011.017.00005 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Alpha Omicron Pi] Theta Delta Chi gets 123 house; Phil Abruzzi. Korandanis, Arthur returns as Director of Dining Services. ACCESS; editorials; pp. 2,13; [African-American Center] TCU-S discusses South African scholarship, p. 1, 3.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 14; UP029.011.017.00006 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 17; UP029.011.017.00007 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Administration] Fundraising breaks record, p. 1, 2.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 18; UP029.011.017.00008 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Administration] Campus reacts to anti-catholic material, p. 5; Student Socolow transfers without filing suit, p. 1, 11; [African-American Center] Memorial service for Jewel Hariston Bell, p. 1.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 19; UP029.011.017.00009 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)
    [Alpha Sigma Phi] Alcohol Policy. [African-American Center] Sponsors Rev. Mwadime, p. 3, 6. [Alpha Epsilon Pi] Alcohol Policy.
  - Tufts Daily, 1990 September 20; UP029.011.017.00010 (Volume UP029 Shared 3)